Guide to the Edwin H. Armstrong papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Alphabetical Files, 1886-1980
  - Shouse, James--General, 1946 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Shute, E.R.--"The Varioplex-A New Development in Telegraphy," 1940 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Simon, I.--"Forces Acting on Superconductors in Magnetic Fields," 1953 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Simon, Leslie--"On Bridging the Gap Between Research and Development," 1952 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Skinner, Cook--Correspondence, 1949-1953 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Slaby, A.--"A New Telegraphy," 1898 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Sleeper, Milton--Correspondence, 1941-1953 (Box 117, Folder 13-14)
  - Smith, C.H.--"Note on the Relationships Existing Between Radio Waves Modulated in Frequency and in Amplitude," 1930 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Smith, D.B. and W.E. Bradley--"The Theory of Impulse Noise in Ideal Frequency Modulation Receivers," 1946 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Smith, H.P.--"Transmission Line Calculator," 1939 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Soucy, C.I.--"Temperature Coefficients in Electronic Circuits," 1948 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Spingarn, J.H.--"Radio is Yours," 1946 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Southampton, New York--Receiving Tests, 1950 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Sponsor Magazine--Report and Correspondence, 1951 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Squire, G.--"Multiplex Telephony and Telegraphy Over Open-Circuit Bare Wires Laid in the Earth or Sea," 1920 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - "Multiplex Telephony and Telegraphy by Means of Electric Waves Guided by Wires," 1911 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Stanton's Electric and Communications Digest--Articles, 1949-1954, (2 Folders) (Box 117, Folder 24-25)
  - Static
    - Early Notes, Diagrams and Data, undated (Box 117, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified Oscillograms, undated (Box 117, Folder 27)
    - Oscillograms, 1929 June 18 (Box 117, Folder 28)
    - Siphon Recorder Tape of Armstrong Experiments "Single Z and Balance Sending," 1927 March-April, (2 Folders) (Box 117, Folder 29-30)
    - Short Wave--General, 1952 (Box 117, Folder 31)
    - Diagrams, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 117, Folder 32-33)
    - Siphon Recorder Tape of Demo by Armstrong to Sarnoff and Winterbottom at Columbia Hartley Research Center--Exhibit Z, 1927 (Box 117, Folder 34)
    - Siphon Recorder Tape of Experiments, 1927-1929, (4 Folders) (Box 117, Folder 35-39)
    - Siphon Recorder Tapes of Experiments, 1927 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Signal-Static Calculations, undated (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Diagrams, undated (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Explanation of Void Ratio--Notes, undated (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Steinman, David--General, 1952-1953 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Sterling, George--General, 1947-1948 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Stetson, Harlan T.--General, 1948-1949 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Stevenson, A.R. and S. Ramo--"A New Course in Industry in High Frequency Engineering," 1940 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Stokowski, Leopold--"New Vistas in Radio," 1935 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Stricker, Adam--Correspondence, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Stromberg-Carlson Telephone Manufacturing Co.--General, 1939-1952, (2 Folders) (Box 118, Folder 11-12)
    - "Investigation of 'Narrow Band' vs. 'Wide Band' Frequency Modulation System"--Report, 1940 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Strutt, M.J.O--Articles, 1946 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Stumpers, F.L.H.M.--"Some Investigations Regarding Vibrations with Frequency Modulation "--Thesis and Correspondence, 1946 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - "The Determination of the Distortion in a Frequency Modulator," 1948 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - "The Phase Discriminator: Its Use as Frequency-Amplitude Converter for FM Reception," 1944 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Sturley, K.R.--"Frequency Modulation," 1945 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Sullivan, J.F.--"Low Loss Voice," 1925 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Summerhayes, H.R.--"Frequency-Modulation Station Monitor," 1943 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - "260-350 Megacycle Converter Unit for G.E. Frequency-Modulation Station Monitor," 1943 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Litigation
    - Armstrong v. Sylvania Electric Products, Inc.
      - Pleadings, 1956 (Box 118, Folder 22)
      - Data for Argument of Motion, 1955 (Box 118, Folder 23)
      - Data, Legal Documents and Papers Not Used, 1955 (Box 118, Folder 24)
      - Data for Brief and Argument on Motion, 1955 (Box 118, Folder 25)
      - Contract, 1943-1945 (Box 118, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence on War Department Equipment, 1943-1944 (Box 118, Folder 27)
      - Technical Section of the Sylvania News Articles, 1949-1954 (Folder 28)
        - Sylvania News Index, 1946-1949 (Box 118, Folder 29)
  - Swift, Gilbert--Amplifier Testing by Means of Square Waves, 1939 (Box 118, Folder 30)
  - Swinton, A.A.C.--"Demonstration of the Wehnelt Electrolytic Contact-Breaker," 1899 (Box 118, Folder 31)
  - Tape (Magnetic) Recordings-12" (Box 261)
    - "W2AG--Frequency vs. Amplitude"--"Continental Dance Music," undated (Box 261)
    - "RCA Test Cuts," undated (Box 261)
    - "Haddonfield AM-FM Comparison 1935," 1948 (Box 261)
    - Ampex 406 Reel to Reel Recordings
      - Tape Recording 3a, 3b, 4--NBC, 1947 July 3 (3 reel to reels) (Box 261)
  - Audio Cassette
    - "Copy of Armstrong Tape of July, 2, 1947" (Box 261)
  - Tarzian, Sarkes--General, 1944 (Box 118, Folder 32)
  - Taylor, A.H.--Letter to Fortune Magazine Stating that Armstrong is not the Inventor of FM, 1939 (Box 118, Folder 33)
  - Technical Appliance Co. (TACO)--Correspondence and Catalogs, 1952-1954 (Box 118, Folder 34)
  - Tele-Tech Coverage of FM vs. AM, 1949 (Box 118, Folder 35)
  - Television
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 118, Folder 36)
    - General, 1947-1953, (2 Folders) (Box 119, Folder 1-2)
    - Color, 1944-1953 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - "Television: Its Development and Accomplishment"--Bell Labs Booklet, 1927 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Picture and Sound Carriers, undated (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Articles, 1940 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - "Interim Report on the Design and Development of a UHF Television Transmitting Antenna," 1952 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Interference--Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Tesla, Nikola--General, 1943-1954 (Folder 9)
    - Articles, 1900-1904 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Terman, F.E.--"Radio Engineering," 1932 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Terman, F.E. and N.R. Morgan--"Some Properties of Grid Leak Power Detection," 1930 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Thatcher, E.W.--"On the Reduction of Shot Effect Fluctuations by Electron Space Charge," 1932 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Thomson, E.--"Dynamic Induction at High Potentials and Frequencies," undated (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Thompson, J.J.--"On Some of the Consequences of the Emission of Negatively Electrified Corpuscles by Hot Bodies," 1902 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Tiberio, U.--"Measure of Distance by Means of Ultra Short Wave (Radio Telemetry)," 1939 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Tillman, J.R.--"Linear Frequency Discriminator," 1946 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Tilton, Edward P--"New Theories on VHF Wave Reduction," 1952 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Titanic--”Role of Radio Reception in Rescue Efforts," 1953 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Train Radio--Articles, 1945-1946 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - Turner, P.K.--"A New Valve Characteristic," 1932 (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - "U-H-F Technique," 1942 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - Underhill, C.R.--Correspondence (Photographs), 1935-1953 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - Tobey, Charles W.--General, 1947-1950, (2 Folders) (Box 119, Folder 24-25)
  - Unites States Air Force Contracts
    - Contract #W28-099 ac-14--General, 1945-1953, (3 Folders) (Box 119, Folder 26-28)
      - Termination, 1953 (Box 119, Folder 29)
      - General, 1945-1950, (2 Folders) (Box 119, Folder 30-31)
    - Contract #W28-003-sc-248--General, 1943-1944 (Box 119, Folder 32)
    - Contract #W28-099 ac-14
      - Packing Lists--Government Furnished Property, 1945-1952 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - Government Property and GFP Status, 1945-1952 (Box 120, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1949-1953 (Box 120, Folder 3)
      - Radar Transmitter Log, undated (Box 120, Folder 4)
      - Operating Instructions High Power Frequency Modulation Doppler Radar System, undated (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Contract #AF19 (604)-889, Cambridge Research Center
      - General, 1951-1954, (2 Folders) (Box 120, Folder 6-7)
      - Vouchers, 1946-1954 (Box 120, Folder 8)
      - Orders, 1953-1954 (Box 120, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 120, Folder 10)
      - Requisitions for Payments, 1954-1955 (Box 120, Folder 11)
      - Supply Orders, 1953-1954 (Box 120, Folder 12)
      - General, 1953 (Box 120, Folder 13)
      - Account Log--Disbursements and Receipts, 1946-1953 (Box 248)
    - Contract #W28-099 ac-14
      - Collins Radio Co., 1948-1952 (Box 120, Folder 14)
      - General, 1945-1953 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Security, Agreements and Correspondence, 1949-1954 (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Data Lists, Equipment Specifications and Service Test Reports, 1945 (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - "Proposal for Project MX1179 Integrated Interceptor Electronic and Control System," 1950 (Box 120, Folder 18)
    - General, 1943 (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - "Preliminary Descriptive Specifications: Projection Console for Signal Corps," 1943 (Box 120, Folder 20)
    - "Maintenance Parts List for Radio and Radar Equipment," 1945 (Box 120, Folder 21)
    - "Report on Calibration and Evaluation Test Series SCR-602 Radar-Air Defense Board Project No. 85 and 52," 1943 (Box 120, Folder 22)
    - "Report on Calibration of the SCR-271-D at Orlo Vista, Florida," undated (Box 120, Folder 23)
    - Radio Equipment Proposals, 1943-1944 (Box 120, Folder 24)
    - "Jamming Tests Against the Orlando Air Defense System-Report," 1943 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Signal Corps Contract Records--General, 1941-1948, (2 Folders) (Box 121, Folder 2-3)
    - Contract #W28-099 ac-14--Receipts and Disbursements, 1946 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - General, 1941-1959, (2 Folders) (Box 121, Folder 5-6)
    - Air Corps Contract Requisitions, 1946-1952 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 1947-1953 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Orders Completed, 1945-1952, (6 Folders) (Box 121, Folder 9-14)
    - General--Includes Contract Correspondence Regarding Patent Applications and Changes, 1940-1948 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Blueprints, 1940 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - "Preliminary Instruction Book NLS-667 Tripler and 600Mc. Amplifier," 1945 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - "Preliminary Instruction Book NLS-667 Tripler and 600Mc. Amplifier," 1945, (2 Folders) (Box 122, Folder 1-2)
    - "The Maximum Range of a Radar Set," 1943 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Pilotless Aircraft Report, undated (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Radar Report, undated (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - General, 1939 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Radio Set Blueprints, 1940 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Bills Paid through E.H. Armstrong Account No. 2, 1946-1948, (5 Folders) (Box 122, Folder 9-13)
    - Account Book, 1951 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - "The Effect of Jamming on the Maximum Range of a Radar Set," 1943 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Radar Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Summary of Comparative Tests of Radio Set SCR-508 and British Wireless Set No. 19, 1942 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Bills Paid through E.H. Armstrong Account No. 2, 1950, (5 Folders) (Box 122, Folder 18-22)
    - Contract W28-099 ac-14
      - Bills Paid Through E.H. Armstrong Account No. 2, 1951-1953, (6 Folders) (Box 123, Folder 1-6)
    - Contract #AF19 (604)-889--Bills Paid, Charges, 1953-1954, (3 Folders) (Box 123, Folder 7-9)
    - Bills Paid Through E.H. Armstrong Account No. 2, 1949, (3 Folders) (Box 123, Folder 10-12)
    - FM Warning Equipment (Experimental Pre-service Test Model), 1943 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - E. H. Armstrong Account No. 2--Statements, 1946-1953 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Account Book, 1946-1950, (2 Folders) (Box 123, Folder 15-16)
    - Contract W28-099 ac-14
      - "High Power Frequency Modulation Doppler Radar System"--Final Report, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 225, Folder 1-2)
        - "Operating Instructions," undated (Box 225, Folder 3)
      - Radar Development Notes--Includes Schematics--Robert Hull, 1944-1953 (Box 225, Folder 4)
      - Patent for Radar--United States Application No. 794,608, Filed 1947 December 30, 1943-1955 (Box 225, Folder 5)
      - High Power Generator--Propagation--Reference Articles and Reports, 1944-1950 (Box 225, Folder 6)
      - Logbooks for Armstrong Lab--Alpine, New Jersey--Robert Hull, 1947 June-1954 March, (6 Folders) (Box 225, Folder 7-12)
      - Photographs, 1948-1950 (Box 225, Folder 13-14)
    - Contacts--General, 1953-1959 (Box 225, Folder 15)
    - Contract No. W28-099 ac 14 (Box 248)
      - Armstrong Laboratory, Alpine, NJ--Preliminary Drawings and Photographs--Department of the Air Force, 3151st Electronics Station, Watson Laboratories, Red Bank, NJ, 1948-1949 (2 copies) (Box 248 (flat))
    - Armstrong Laboratory, Alpine, New Jersey--Recorded Signal at Alpine--400 Mc Rd. Hill, Massachusetts (Robert Hull), 1953 November-December (4 rolls) (Box 249)
    - First 425 Mc Recording--Southampton, New York (Shinnecock Hills, Long Island), 1950 October 27 (in Box) (Box 249)
    - Project Lincoln
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) Department of Electrical Engineering Booklet, 1952-1953 (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - General, 1950-1953, (4 Folders) (Box 124, Folder 2-5)
      - Invoices, 1953 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Research Laboratory of Electronics-Quarterly Progress Report, 1953 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - MIT Bulletin, 1952-1953 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - "High Power Frequency Modulation Doppler Radar System"--Armstrong Lab, Alpine, NJ--W28-099 ac-14--Final Report, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 124, Folder 9-10)
    - Security Questionnaire, 1944 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Early Records of 5 Meter Transmissions, 1930-1931 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Personnel Clearance Matters, 1946-1947 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Contract #W28-003-SC-248--Signal Corp Communications, 1943-1946 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Security Information, 1953 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - United States Army
    - "Leap Frog Telephones in the Military"--Press Release, 1945 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Equipment Orders, 1943 (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Antenna Data--Includes Photographs, 1943-1944 (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Authorization and Visit to Alpine, 1942-1947 (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Signal Corps Contract, 1940-1952 (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - Report of the Chief Signal Officer, US Army, to the Secretary of War--Booklet, 1920 (Box 124, Folder 22)
    - "A Method of Transmitting the Telegraph Alphabet Applicable for Radio, Land Lines and Submarine Cables," by George Squire, 1923 (Box 124, Folder 23)
    - Blueprints, 1942-1944, (2 Folders) (Box 125, Folder 1-2)
    - American Expeditionary Forces(AEF)--Signal Corps
      - No. I--File No. 201--Officer E.H. Armstrong, 1917-1919 (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - No. II--File Known as "Envelope in E and R Safe, Marked "AEF Patents--Armstrongs' Superheterodyne," 1918 (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - No. III--File No. 336.6--Interallied Radio Telegraph Commission, 1918-1919 (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - No. IV--File No. 413.44 (U.S.) 13--Development of Radio Equipment, 1917 (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - No. V--File No. 413.44--Amplifiers, High Frequency--Report of Armstrong, 1919 (Box 125, Folder 7)
      - No. VI--File No. 201--Officer H.E. Shreeve, 1917 (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - No. VII--File No. 314.7, Folder No. 2--Personal Histories, 1916 (Box 125, Folder 9)
      - No. VIII--File No. 321.91--Research and Inspection, 1917 (Box 125, Folder 10)
      - No. IX--File No. 319.1--Research and Inspection, 1916 (Box 125, Folder 11)
      - No. X--File No. 314.7, Folder No. 1--"History of Research and Inspection, Div AEF," undated (Box 125, Folder 12)
      - No. XI--File No. 314.7--History of the Activities of the Radio Division of the Chief Signal Officer, AEF, undated (Box 125, Folder 13)
      - No. XII--File No. 319.1--Miscellaneous Reports--Kennelly Report, 1918 (Box 125, Folder 14)
      - No. XIII-File No. 319.1--Monthly Reports of the Chief Signal Officer of AEF, 1917-1919 (Box 125, Folder 15)
      - No. XIV--File No. 413.4--Radio, 1919 (Box 125, Folder 16)
      - No. XV--File No. 413.4--Amplifiers (Telephone), 1919 (Box 125, Folder 17)
      - "Signal Communications for All Arms," 1919 (Box 125, Folder 18)
      - French Manuals and Reports, 1917-1919, (2 Folders) (Box 125, Folder 19-20)
      - General, 1917-1919 (Box 125, Folder 21)
      - Blueprints--Division of Research and Inspection, Radio Department--Armstrong High Frequency Amplifier--Armstrong High Frequency Receiver Amplifier System--Assembly, 1918 (Box 99)
    - Death Ray--Correspondence and License Agreement, 1942-1943 (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - US Atomic Energy Commission
    - Atomic Energy Programs Reports, 1950-1952 (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - US Bureau of Standards
    - Articles, 1950-1953 (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - General, 1923-1953 (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - Articles from Bulletin, 1907-1922 (Box 125, Folder 25)
    - Circular of the Bureau of Standards: "Radio Instruments and Measurements," 1918 (Box 125, Folder 26)
    - "Electronic Phase Meter," by E. Florman and A. Tart, 1948 (Box 125, Folder 27)
    - Minutes of Open Meetings of Department of Conference on Radio Telephony, 1922 (Box 125, Folder 28)
    - "Sunspots and Very High Frequency Radio Transmission," by Kenneth Norton, 1947 (Box 125, Folder 29)
  - House of Representatives
    - Volumes
      - Hearings before the Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations House of Representatives, Seventy-Ninth Congress, Second Session on the Independent Offices Appropriation Bill for 1947 (Box 125)
      - Hearings before the Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations House of Representatives, Seventy-Ninth Congress, First Session on the Independent Offices Appropriation Bill for 1946 (Box 125)
      - Hearings Before the Subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations House of Representatives, Eightieth Congress, Second Session on the Independent Offices Appropriation Bill for 1949 (Box 132)
    - Statement of Armstrong Prepared for Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1948 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - HR 11964 1922 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Frequency Modulation Witnesses Noble and Jolliffe--Transcript of Hearing, 1948 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - General, 1943-1952 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Education and Labor--Petrillo Hearing, 1946-1948 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Investigation of FCC--Including FM, 1949 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Lemke Bill--FM on Low Band--Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Lemke Bill--HJ Res. 78--General, 1948 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - United States Senate
    - General, 1949-1953, (2 Folders) (Box 132, Folder 10-11)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1953 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence with Senate Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1949-1951 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Hearing before Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee--"Progress of FM Radio"--General, 1948, (3 Folders) (Box 132, Folder 14-16)
    - Communications Study--Subcommittee of Interstate and Foreign Commerce (Toby McFarland), 1949 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Congressional Records, 1951 (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Hearings
      - "Certain Charges Involving Development of FM Radio and RCA Patent Policies," 1948 (Box 132, Folder 19)
      - "The Nomination of Edward Mount Webster of the District of Columbia, to be a Member of the Federal Communications Commission for a 7 year Term Beginning in July," 1949 (Box 132, Folder 20)
      - "A Bill to Amend the Communications Act of 1934 As Amended," 1949 (Box 132, Folder 21)
      - "A Bill to Amend the Communications Act of 1934 and For Other Purposes," 1947 (Box 132, Folder 22)
      - "Hearings Before the Senate Interstate Commerce Committee," 1948 (Box 133, Folder 1)
      - "To Amend the Communications Act of 1934," 1943 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      - Hearing on Bill S.1333 "To Amend the Communications Act of 1934"--General, 1947 (Box 133, Folder 3)
      - Official Hearing Before the Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee-Confirmation Coy and Sterling, 1948 (Box 133, Folder 4)
      - Hearings on S.2231--Bill to Limit AM Broadcasting Stations to 50 Kw, 1948 (Box 133, Folder 5)
      - "The Nomination of G.E. Sterling," 1950 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Inquiry into FCC (Including S.1973)--General, 1949, (2 Folders) (Box 133, Folder 7-8)
    - Investigation of Armstrong's Charge of Alternation in FCC Record, 1948 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - The Present Status of Color Television, 1950 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Statement of Honorable Wayne Coy, Chairman of FCC Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1951 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Testimony of Drew Pearson--Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, 1951 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - United States Federal Communications Committee (FCC)
    - Guy Report--Diagrams, 1937 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - General, 1936-1954, (3 Folders) (Box 133, Folder 14-16)
    - Worksheets on FM Brief in Opposition to Reallocation of Band, 1945 (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence with Charles Tobey, 1949-1950 (Box 133, Folder 19)
    - Station License Forms, 1954 (Box 133, Folder 20)
    - Proceedings, 1951 (Box 133, Folder 21)
    - General, 1945-1953, (6 Folders) (Box 136, Folder 1-6)
    - Applications, Printed Reports, Construction Permits for Operating Alpine, 1950-1954, (5 Folders) (Box 136, Folder 7-11)
    - Dow, Lohnes and Albertson--Government Applications, Permits, 1941-1948, (6 Folders) (Box 136, Folder 12-17)
    - Field Survey--Louisville Hi-Lo Band Study, undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Allen's Confidential FCC Memorandum to Sterling, 1947 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence--Includes Excerpts from FCC Files, 1935-1954, (7 Folders) (Box 137, Folder 2-8)
    - Docket #3929--"Presentation for the Amateur Service," 1936 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Docket #5806--Television Hearing, 1940-1941 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Docket #6651--Allocation of Frequencies
      - Papers and Correspondence Relating to Allocation Controversy, 1945, (2 Folders) (Box 137, Folder 11-12)
      - Papers and Correspondence on Zenith's Tests on Both Bands, 1945-1946, (2 Folders) (Box 137, Folder 13-14)
      - Excerpts from Official Testimony, 1944-1946, (3 Folders) (Box 137, Folder 15-17)
      - Briefs, 1945, (2 Folders) (Box 137, Folder 18-19)
      - Brief for Edwin H. Armstrong in Opposition to Proposed FM Assignments, 1945 February 21 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Supplemental Brief of Edwin H. Armstrong in Opposition to Proposed FM Assignments, 1945 February 21 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Allocation of Frequencies to the Various Classes of Non-governmental Services in the Radio Spectrum from 10 kilocycles to 30,000,000 kilocycles, 1945 April 25 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Official Report of Proceedings, 1946 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Section 8--FM Broadcasting Service, 1945 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Briefs and Statements, 1945 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Radio Technical Planning Board
        - Committee 6--Relay Links--Panel 6 Television, 1944 (Box 138, Folder 4)
        - Report on Standards and Frequency Allocations for Postwar Broadcasting--Panel 5, 1944 (Box 138, Folder 5)
        - Report on Standards and Frequency Allocations for Postwar Television--Panel 6--Television, 1944 (Box 138, Folder 6)
        - Second Report on Standards and Frequency Allocations for Postwar Television--Panel 6--Television, 1944 (Box 138, Folder 7)
        - Committee 1--Television Channel--Panel 6--Television, 1944 (Box 138, Folder 8)